Guide to the Dwight L. Moody Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Sermons, Series II
  - Centenary Committee Publications
    - Moody's Illustrations (Box 13, Folder 67)
    - The Prodigal Son (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - The Good Samaritan (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - The Prophet Daniel (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Saul of Tarsus (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - Zaccheus (Box 13, Folder 68)
    - The Incurables (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - The Widow of Nain (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Some Blind Men (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - The Lame Man Healed (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Major-General Naaman (Box 13, Folder 69)
- Journals, Clippings, Articles About Moody, Series III
  The two journals included in this section were written by Mrs. Jane MacKinnon and Emma C. Moody during the Great Britain campaign of 1873-1875. Also included is an autograph book belonging to Emma Moody, dating 1884-1890.
  General articles about Moody's life have been arranged chronologically, followed by articles by more notable persons which have been arranged alphabetically by author.
  Addresses, articles and publications arising from the celebration of the Moody Centenary in 1937 have been grouped separately.
  Clippings describing the New York campaign of 1876 and the New Haven campaign of 1878 are arranged chronologically.
  The last folder in this series contains a D.L. Moody bibliography compiled by A.P. Fitt in 1935.
  The series is completed by two bound volumes, scrapbooks containing clippings about evangelistic campaigns and about the deaths of D.L. Moody and Mrs. D.L. Moody.
  - General articles
    - Journal of Mrs. Jane MacKinnon, 1874 (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Journal of Emma C. Moody, 1873-1875 (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Autograph Book of Emma C. Moody, 1884-1890 (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Articles and Clippings on Moody incl. program of Memorial service, 1892-1900 (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Articles and Clippings on Moody, 1903-1915 (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Articles and Clippings on Moody, 1923-1943 (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Articles and Clippings from Scrapbook (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Articles and Clippings from Scrapbook (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Articles and Clippings from Scrapbook (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Articles by more notable authors
    - Abbott, Lyman, 1921 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Douglas, Walter C., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Drummond, Henry (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Grenfell, Wilfred T., 1907 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Magoun, George, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - McDowell, John, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Paul D. Moody on D.L. Moody, 1923, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - William R. Moody on D.L. Moody (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Morgan, G. Campbell, 1889 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Morris, George Perry, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Morse, Richard C., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - John R. Mott on D.L. Moody, 1915,1935, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Rankin, Henry W., 1936 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Sprunt, James, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Stebbins, George C, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Trumbull, H. Clay, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 15)
  - Publications related to Moody Centenary
    - Centenary Celebration Clippings, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Centenary Addresses, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - Centenary Addresses, New York Mass Meeting, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - British Centenary Addresses, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Addresses on Christ and the Bible, Northfield, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Publications of Centenary Committee, 1937 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - Publications related to evangelistic campaigns
    - Clippings from New York Campaign, 1876 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Clippings from New Haven Campaign: March 29-April 5, 1878 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Clippings from New Haven Campaign: April 6-April 20 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Clippings from New Haven Campaign: April 22-May 7 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Clippings from New Haven Campaign: May 9-May 28 (Box 16, Folder 26)
  - Additional material
    - D.L. Moody Bibliography by A.P. Fitt, 1935 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Clippings about Evangelistic Campaigns, 1875-1895 (Box OV1)
    - Clippings about deaths of D.L. Moody and Mrs. D.L. Moody, 1899, 1903 (Box OV1)